songs.pk 2013-01-15

# Songs.PK - Privacy Policy

  |  |  |  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|  |  |  |   
  |   
  |   
| 

[Home](http://www.songspk.pk/) | Bollywood Songs | Pakistani Songs  | Indian Pop And Remix Songs | Bhangra Songs | Ghazals | Contact Us

|   
|   
|  |   
  |   
| 

|   |  |  | 

**Privacy Policy - Songs.PK**

|  | 

**Privacy Policy**

 **Privacy Statement for** Songs.PK  
Songs.PK  has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Songs.PK 

**Third Party Cookies**

Third Party Cookies In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies.

**External Links**  
Songs.PK contains links of other sites on the internet. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of web sites we link to. We do make an effort to avoid linking to known "adult" and "porn" sites. Songs.PK is a family web site.

**Changes To Our Privacy Policy**  
To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we reserve the right to change or replace this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time without prior notice to or the consent of any person. Any changes or replacement will be posted at this site.

 **Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [ http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).  
  
---  
|  |  |   
|  |  |   

popular tags: **[ race 2 movie songs](http://music.songs.pk/indian/race_2_2013_mp3_songs.html),** **[ rahat fateh ali khan songs](http://www.songspk.pk/artists.html), download free music, hindi mp3 music, [ download dabangg 2 songs](http://music.songs.pk/indian/dabangg_2_2012_mp3_songs.html), [matru ki bijlee ka mandola mp3 songs](http://url2.bollywoodmp3.se/matru_ki_bijlee_ka_mandola_single_2012_mp3_songs.php), indian mp3 rips, [ race 2 320kbps mp3 songs](http://www.songspk.pk/indian/race_2_2013_mp3_songs.html), download cd rip, 320 kbps mp3 download, [raaz 3 mp3 music](http://www.songspk.pk/indian/raaz_3_2012_mp3_songs.html), free flac music, mp3 music of dabangg 2, [hindi songs download of rush](http://music.songs.pk/indian/rush_2012_mp3_songs.html), [download latest bollywood songs](http://www.songspk.pk/bollywood_songs.html), [listen akaash vani mp3 music](http://music.songs.pk/indian/akaash_vani_2013_mp3_songs.html), flac rips, free 128 kbps quality songs, [ bollywood music download](http://www.songspk.pk/bollywood_songs.html), [free table no 21 songs](http://www.songspk.pk/indian/table_no_21_2012_mp3_songs.html), latest indian songs, bollywood music download, [ khiladi 786 mp3 download](http://music.songs.pk/indian/khiladi_786_2012_mp3_songs.html), [raaz 3 mp3 songs](http://www.songspk.pk/indian/raaz_3_2012_mp3_songs.html), [download ek tha tiger mp3 songs](http://bollywoodmp3hits.com/bollywood-mp3-songs/ek-tha-tiger-2012-download-mp3-songs/),  pakistani music, [ jab tak hai jaan mp3 music download](http://music.songs.pk/indian/jab_tak_hai_jaan_2012_mp3_songs.html), [download matru ki bijlee ka mandola songs](http://url2.bollywoodmp3.se/matru_ki_bijlee_ka_mandola_single_2012_mp3_songs.php), [race 2 Mp3 Songs](http://music.songs.pk/indian/race_2_2013_mp3_songs.html), [Download son of sardaar songs](http://www.songspk.pk/indian/son_of_sardaar_2012_mp3_songs.html), [ aiyyaa mp3 songs download](http://music.songs.pk/indian/aiyyaa_2012_mp3_songs.html), [download raaz 3 mp3 songs](http://www.songspk.pk/indian/raaz_3_2012_mp3_songs.html), download mp3 torrents, [ songspk A List](http://music.songs.pk/a_list.html), [ SongsPk B List](http://music.songs.pk/b_list.html), [ SongsPK C List](http://music.songs.pk/c_list.html), [ Songspk D List](http://music.songs.pk/d_list.html), [ E List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/e_list.html), [ S List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/s_list.html), [ T List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/t_list.html), [ M List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/m_list.html), [ N List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/n_list.html), [ K List](http://music.songs.pk/k_list.html) , [ G List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/g_list.html), [ H List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/h_list.html), [ I List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/i_list.html), [ J List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/j_list.html), [ L List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/l_list.html), [ L List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/l_list.html), [ O List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/o_list.html), [ P List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/p_list.html), [ R List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/r_list.html), [ Y List Songspk](http://music.songs.pk/y_list.html)**

|   
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |   
  | 

Copyrights Reserved By Songs.PK  
  
|  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |  |
